build-success-online.com 2012-03-23

# Privacy Policy | Build-Success-Online.com/blog

## Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Build-Success-Online.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. 

Additionally some of the links you find on this website are affiliate links. If you click on a link from this webspage, and buy a product there is a good chance we will benfit from the purchase of that product. Thank you for doing business with the companies we recommend. 

Additionally, although every measure is made to assure the security of the sites we recommend, we can’t guarantee it, because they aren’t our sites. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. 

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Build-Success-Online.com then you may contact us at armyvic82@hotmail.com 

Last updated Tue, 15 Mar 2011 12:02
